# Can Bartu Kılıç

## Web & Mobile Developer



Beylikdüzü, İstanbul

+90 537 205 1022 canbartuklc@gmail.com

github.com/cbartuk

linkedin.com/in/cbartuk/



twitter.com/SenatorMaul



http://cbartuk.com/

#### **Skills**

JavaScript React.is

Node.js

HTML / CSS (Bootstrap, Tailwind etc.)

Git

Ethers.js

Kotlin

**Product Design and Development** 

Lifecycle

Marketing

**Business Development** 

#### **Certificates**

JavaScript (Basic) Java (Basic) SQL (Basic) Kotlin 101

#### Languages

Turkish (Native) English (Professional working proficiency B1)

#### **About Me**

I am 26 years old and I live in Istanbul. I have been interested in electronics since childhood. This curiosity led me to make robots and to learn how to program them. That journey continued with a fast and comprehensive entry to the software world. I have focused rowing and enhancing my skillset consists of all these areas. I believe that the learning process is an ongoing lifestyle. Through all the education and experience I had in my career; As the intersection point of my childhood dreams and my professional career, led me to commit to work on Software Engineering. My main goal in this field is being productive to solve real life problems by having a pragmatic mindset. Currently, I am advancing my career in web programming and mobile programming. I am currently doing Micro Master on Mobile Applications at HarvardX.

### **Experiences**

#### BiLira Technology Inc. / Blockchain Researcher

MARCH 2022 - NOW, ISTANBUL

- Blockchain 101 book authorship
- Article and social media writing
- Marketing and Brand Department content producer(Details are in the 'Projects' section)
- Event and seminar speaker as a company representative
- Improving brand awareness, managing influencer marketing processes

#### BiLira Technology Inc. / Operation Specialist

JANUARY 2022 - MARCH 2022, ISTANBUL

- Development of auxiliary tools and methods for continuous analysis and improvement of working processes
- Customer support processes related to products and services
- Monitoring of departmental activities

#### MD KALIP/ADAL PANO / R&D Engineer

JUL 2020 - NOV 2021, ISTANBUL

- Robotic coding
- Practicing designer
- Functional application and production management
- Internal application development for quality control monitoring

TECH STACK: C++ | C# | Arduino | HTML | CSS | Javascript

#### Education

#### **Istanbul Arel University**

2014 - 2019, Türkiye

B.D. Electric Electronic Engineer GPA: 3.46

#### **Harvard University**

2022-2023, ABD (Remote)

M.M. Computer Science & Mobile Apps

**GPA: Continues** 

#### Nevbahar MALL Uskudar(Kalyon & Noya Electric) /

#### **Construction Manager**

OCT 2018 - MAY 2020, ISTANBUL

- Comprehensive project management and field coordinator
- Project design and management of creative teams
- Project link: https://nevbaharuskudar.com/

**TECH STACK: AUTOCAD** 

#### Prysmian (Siemens) Group / Intern R&D Department

JUN 2017 - SEP 2017, BURSA / MUDANYA

- Cable design on Autocad 3D
- Implementing engineer in Turkey submarine fiber cable systems project(I was in the field with the dives.)
- Project link:
  https://www.prysmiangroup.com/staticres/nexst-2017-4/article
  -6.html

TECH STACK: AUTOCAD, SQL

### References

Ahmet Aygün, CxO @Stealth Startup, @BiLira me@ahmetaygun.net

Toprak Keskin, Software Engineer @BiLira Ex Yapı Kredi Technology toprak.keskin@bilira.co

Orhun Özer, Senior Frontend Dev. @Getir

orhun.ozer@getir.com

#### **Projects**

#### Within BiLira Company;

#### **Articles I Produced**

JANUARY 2022 - AUGUST 2022

- Akıllı Sözleşmeler (Smart Contracts)
- Web.bi Topluluğu
- Lending Nedir?

#### **Trainings and Seminars I Provide**

JANUARY 2022 - AUGUST 2022

- İstanbul Üniversitesi İktisat Fakültesi Blockchain A.M.A. Etkinliği
- Solidity Workshop #1 #2
- Beykent Üniversitesi BUTechDays'22
- İstanbul Üniversitesi Cerrahpaşa Mühendislik Fakültesi NFT101
  Eğitim
- Cukurova Üniversitesi Blockchain 101 Eğitim
- Türk Alman Üniversitesi Blockchain 101 Eğitim

#### Videos

JANUARY 2022 - AUGUST 2022

- İslem Kimliği (Tx hash/ID) nedir? | Nedir Serisi #2
- Bittrex Borsasını Keşfedin! | BiLira Kullanım Alanları #12
- Liquid Borsasını Keşfedin! | BiLira Kullanım Alanları #13
- HYVE Platformunu kesfedin! I BiLira Kullanım Alanları #14
- Metavest Uygulamasını Keşfedin! | BiLira Kullanım Alanları #15